{
    "id": "710413737bfb4c02874a1e6367a83cad",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………….. you mind posting this letter for me?",
            "description": "Would is used in polite requests.",
            "answers": [
                "Could",
                "Would",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… you lend me your bicycle?",
            "description": "Will is used in polite requests.",
            "answers": [
                "Shall",
                "Will",
                "May"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………….. not come to my door again.",
            "description": "Shall can express an order when used with second and third person pronouns.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "shall",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………….. regret this.",
            "description": "When used with second and third person pronouns, shall can express a threat. ",
            "answers": [
                "shall",
                "may",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What ……………………….. we do now?",
            "description": "Shall can be used to request instruction.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "shall",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Parents ………………………… teach their children to be honest.",
            "description": "Should expresses duty.",
            "answers": [
                "shall",
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………. take rest if he is tired.",
            "description": "We can use can to express permission.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "can",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………………….. have told me before borrowing my car.",
            "description": "The expression should have is used to criticize people for not doing things.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The students asked if they ………………………. go home early.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "could",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… run faster when I was younger.",
            "description": "Could indicates past ability.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………. not light a match. Gas is leaking.",
            "description": "Must indicates prohibition.",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "should",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………. smoke before I fell ill.",
            "description": "We use used to to talk about past habits. ",
            "answers": [
                "was used to",
                "used to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}